(Penny:)Whoa.
(Penny:)- When would you leave?
- Couple of weeks.
(Leonard:)Wow.
(Penny:)- Okay, well, I'll just come visit you.
- That's the thing, you can't.
(Leonard:)I'll be on a ship in the North Sea.
(Penny:)On a ship? Aren't they afraid
Hawking will just roll overboard?
(Leonard:)He's not gonna be there. He's just
sending a team to research his theory.
(Penny:)Oh, sure. Like when you send me
to kill spiders in your bathtub.
Oh. Okay. So four months.
(Sheldon:)Yeah.
(Leonard:)And I'm a little worried because
things between us have been so great...
(Leonard:)...and I'd hate to do anything
that screws that up.
(Penny:)If you're gonna screw things up...
(Penny:)...it's gonna be while you're here,
not while you're away.
(Penny:)I mean, look, you have to go.
It sounds like an amazing opportunity.
(Penny:)And I'm just basing that on how much
I didn't understand what you said about it.